<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aiven Operator</title><link>https://aiven.github.io/aiven-operator/</link><description>Recent content on Aiven Operator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://aiven.github.io/aiven-operator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kafka Schema</title><link>https://aiven.github.io/aiven-operator/docs/resources/kafka/schema/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aiven.github.io/aiven-operator/docs/resources/kafka/schema/</guid><description>Creating a KafkaSchema Aiven develops and maintain Karapace, an open source implementation of Kafka REST and schema registry. Is available out of the box for our managed Kafka service.
The schema registry address and authentication is the same as the Kafka broker, the only different is the usage of the port 13044.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s create an Aiven for Apache Kafka service.
Create a file named kafka-sample-schema.yaml and add the content below: apiVersion: aiven.</description></item><item><title>Kafka Connect</title><link>https://aiven.github.io/aiven-operator/docs/resources/kafka/connect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aiven.github.io/aiven-operator/docs/resources/kafka/connect/</guid><description>Aiven for Apache Kafka Connect is a framework and a runtime for integrating Kafka with other systems. Kafka connectors can either be a source (for pulling data from other systems into Kafka) or sink (for pushing data into other systems from Kafka).
This section involves a few different Kubernetes CRDs:
A KafkaService service with a KafkaTopic A KafkaConnect service A ServiceIntegration to integrate the Kafka and KafkaConnect services A PostgreSQL used as a sink to receive messages from Kafka A KafkaConnector to finally connect the Kafka with the PostgreSQL Creating the resources Create a file named kafka-sample-connect.</description></item></channel></rss>